Hi!
In this video clip, I will be showing you how to properly mark for an electrical box.
On this section of wall, I want an electrical box to go right here.
If I stick it on there and just mark around my electrical box, there is a good chance that my box is going to be crooked and its not going to look good.
What I like to do is grab a combination square and some other type of tool that may have a small level built into it.
Go ahead and remove that piece and I have this little level.
Now I've also used a line level in the past which is a real small level or you could just buy a very short level.
Next I am going to put my box onto my wall and set that level on top of it.
I am going to go ahead and adjust it so that my bubble goes in the middle that way I will know that box is perfectly level.
Once I have my box leveled, I am going to remove that level and draw around each side of my box.
When I remove my box, I will have my lines.